

MOHD AIMAN HAKIM

+6

+6011-37987725



mohdaimanhakim.98@gmail.com

Bandar Puncak Alam, Selangor Fresh Graduate.

ABOUT ME

A fresh graduate of Bachelor's degree in electronic telecommunications design engineering with a 3.24 CGPA who is motivated to learn and gain experience for future career advancements. Experience in troubleshooting of testing fixtures and equipment. Also experience in using oscilloscope, multimeter, soldering iron, signal generator etc. Also interested in Web Development and have experience using Laravel, ReactJs, ReactNative, NodeJs, Filament, Bootstrap and Tailwind Css. Also experience in backend skills using ExpressJs, Firebase and MongoDB.

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- Self-motivation and hard work.
- Punctual
- Can work under pressure and meet tight deadlines Can work together while working in
- team groups
- Speak fluent in Malay and intermediate english
- Willing to learn

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Advanced in Microft Power Point, Excel and Word.
- Intermediate on engineering software such as Matlab, CST Studio Suite, Advanced Design System, C Programming, Microsoft Power BI and Scilab
- Beginner in Python, Autocad, Wireshark,
- Web development skills Laravel and React.
- Video editing

REFERENCE

TS DR NAZRI BIN A.KARIM
TD HEPA FTKEN UNIVERSITI MALAYSIA
PERLIS 011-12442340
nazrikarim@unimap.edu.my

WORK HISTORY

INTERNSHIP

FGV Innovation Center December 2018 to April 2019

- Supervising all the IT Infrastructure work at FGV
- Innovation Centre.
- Filing documents, supervise
- contractors and update the engineer upon progress.
- Provide day-to-day support to ensure the smooth running of the computers, network devices, printers as well as end users' requirements.
- Understanding of TCP/IP.

INTERNSHIP (Test Engineering)

BCM Electronics SDN BHD

February 2023 to August 2023

- Attend to troubleshoot Daily Production Line Down time
- Direct involve in Preventive Maintenance on Test Fixtures/ Test Stations
- Escallation on out of control/major downtime issues
- Update Daily TSE Inventory data on Spare Parts.
- Implementation on Test Jig & Fixture Improvement.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Universiti Malaysia Perlis (UniMAP) (2019-2023)

Degree in Engineering Electronic Telecommunication Design (RY41)

CGPA: 3.24

Politeknik Kuala Terengganu (2016-2019)

Diploma in Electronic Communication Engineering (DEP) CGPA: 2.91

EXTRA CURRICULUM ACTIVITIES AND CERTIFICATES

- Microsoft Certified: Power BI Data Analyst Associate (2023)
- Certificate in Completing the Intel Industrial Talk:
- Creating Chips for the Future (2020)
- Participated in Spelling Bee Competition (2017)
 Participated in SUKSIS Border Half Marathon
- Participated in Sharing Moment with Andy Kedar in Theatrical Life (2021)
- Participated in Mental Health Talk: Help Yourself from PIMPIN UniMAP.
- Participated in Seminar Kesukarelawanan Kebangsaan from KPT (2021)
- Participate in Annual General Meeting Sahabat Pusat Islam UniMAP
- Winner of 2022 IEEE Malaysia Section Final Year Project Competition